so you're about to watch a video that's very disturbing
this woman had her car parked illegally running outside of her child's charter school to pick up
her daughter and this police officer who could have written her a ticket decided to arrest her
for it it is obviously disturbing that police officers behave this way however there are a
number of people around her watching this happen
there are a number of men around her watching this happen it escalates
and of course she resists because we should always resist all of us all of the time
and these men one of them holding an umbrella
that's the devil
that police officers
the concept of black on black crime that has been made up by conservatives and by the ruling class
is false however black people watching black people get treated like this by police officers
that is black on black crime
support a real one